

MARCIN WRZOŚ

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PORTFOLIO

PROFILE

I have experience in working on non-commercial projects with senior developers. I am a person who is characterized by a 'can-do' attitude and I am always trying to overcome the issue on my own.

I am able to write responsive pages in React with Typescript in line with the newest standards.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531 Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com

SKILLS

Programming

React, TypeScript, JavaScript, Context API, HTML, CSS (including SASS), bootstrap, webpack, github, SQL

Achievements:

Radio Luz: hosting weekly radio show called Ultradzwięki Toastmasters: practicing public speaking skills Aiesec: marketing promotion of the event Dni Kariery

2017

EDUCATION

Reskilled

Programming mentorship - work with senior developers on non commercial project in React + Typescript 2023 to present

Wrocław University of Economics

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

University of Wrocław

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

PROJECTS

Foodie

Foodie is an application written in React and Typescript with custom hooks like usePagination, useAxios or useMutation, project uses communication via http with the external Api spoonacular. The application is connected to a backend server, which allows users to register and login. The backend server is responsible for storing user data and handling authentication requests. You can find the popular recipes, search for them by a category, specific name, see details of each recipe or add to favourites. Project is hosted on Netlify at this <u>link</u>.

<u>Portfolio</u>

React with Typescript application which depicts my resume. Project is responsive and works on mobile devices. Functions responsible for the Day and Night mode have been moved to Context API. You are able to send me an email by contact form, which is implemented by EmailJS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation Analyst

Axa XL | January 2023 to present

- building and Improving process areas
- coordinating process improvement initiatives

Analyst, Senior Financial Services Operations

Factor Law | October 2020 to December 2022

- · improving the process by VBA,
- coordinating the work allocation across the Negotiator teams

Security and Pricing Data Management Specialist

Credit Suisse | January 2020 to September 2020

· maintaining data of financial instruments and their prices

Data & Document Specialist

UBS | February 2019 to October 2019

providing customer service and support to Front Office

Junior Representative, Reconciliation

BNY Mellon | January 2018 to February 2019

- data investigation using information from different vendors
- reconciliation against broker/custodian statements